Francis D. Donovan Papers
© 2011 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Photographic materials, undated, 1829-1997
  - Subseries A: Prints, undated, 1829-1997
    - Sub-subseries 2: Engines, undated, 1829-1997
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 489, undated (Box 24:, Folder 2509)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 496, undated (Box 24:, Folder 2510)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 807, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2511)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 808, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2512)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 837, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2513)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 902, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2514)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 931, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2515)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 937, 1900 (Box 25:, Folder 2516)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1003, 1947 (Box 25:, Folder 2517)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1017, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2518)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1021, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2519)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1045, circa 1907 (Box 25:, Folder 2520)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1071, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2521)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1081, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2522)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2523)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2224)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2525)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2526)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1935 (Box 25:, Folder 2527)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2528)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2529)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2530)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1094, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2531)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1108, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2532)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1202, 1922 (Box 25:, Folder 2533)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1208, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2534)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1209, 1968 (Box 25:, Folder 2535)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1229, 1968 (Box 25:, Folder 2536)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1229, 1968 (Box 25:, Folder 2537)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1259, 1926 (Box 25:, Folder 2538)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1283, circa 1915 (Box 25:, Folder 2539)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1284, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2540)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1300, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2541)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1312, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2542)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1343, circa 1947 (Box 25:, Folder 2543)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1343, circa 1947 (Box 25:, Folder 2544)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1343, circa 1947 (Box 25:, Folder 2545)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1343, circa 1947 (Box 25:, Folder 2546)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1343, circa 1947 (Box 25:, Folder 2547)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1356, 1920 (Box 25:, Folder 2548)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1356, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2549)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engines 1356 and 2526, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2550)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engines 1345 and 2526, circa 1920 (Box 25:, Folder 2551)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1360, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2552)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1364, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2553)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1403, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2554)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1404, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2555)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1409, 1957 (Box 25:, Folder 2556)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1535, circa 1920 (Box 25:, Folder 2557)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1641, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2558)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engines 1643 and 1672, 1912 (Box 25:, Folder 2559)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1713, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2560)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1732, 1909 (Box 25:, Folder 2561)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 1909, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2562)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 2526, 1920 (Box 25:, Folder 2563)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3013, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2564)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2565)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, 1953 (Box 25:, Folder 2566)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, 1953 (Box 25:, Folder 2567)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, 1953 (Box 25:, Folder 2568)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, 1953 (Box 25:, Folder 2569)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, 1953 (Box 25:, Folder 2570)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, 1953 (Box 25:, Folder 2571)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, 1953 (Box 25:, Folder 2572)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3016, 1953 (Box 25:, Folder 2573)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3018, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2574)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3018, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2575)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3018, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2576)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3018, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2577)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3018, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2578)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3018, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2579)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3018, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2580)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3500, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2581)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, engine 3509, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2582)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, "Franklin local eastbound held at Walpole, Massachusetts, because signals were obliterated by snow," class I-2, 4-6-2, 1938 (Box 28:, Folder 2875)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, unidentified engine, 1946 (Box 25:, Folder 2583)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, unidentified engine, 1946 (Box 25:, Folder 2584)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2585)
      - New York, Ontario & Western Railroad, engine 401, 1922 (Box 25:, Folder 2586)
      - New York, Providence & Boston Railroad, engine 48, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2587)
      - Nickel Plate Railroad, engine 174, circa 1940 (Box 28:, Folder 2818)
      - Nord Railway, engine 2809, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2588)
      - Nord Railway (French), engine 31202, 4-6-2, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2853)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 102, 1934 (Box 25:, Folder 2589)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 122, 1945 (Box 25:, Folder 2590)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 528, 1887 (Box 25:, Folder 2591)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 600, 1942 (Box 25:, Folder 2592)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 1094, 1907 (Box 25:, Folder 2593)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 1100, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2594)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 1200, 1936 (Box 25:, Folder 2595)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 1212, 1943 (Box 25:, Folder 2596)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 1228, 1944 (Box 25:, Folder 2597)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 2124, 1939 (Box 25:, Folder 2598)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 2156, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2599)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 30684, 1943 (Box 25:, Folder 2600)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, engine 31434, 1945 (Box 25:, Folder 2601)
      - Norfolk Company Railroad, "Putnam", 1849 (Box 25:, Folder 2602)
      - North Carolina & Saint Louis Railroad, engine 535, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2603)
      - North Carolina & Saint Louis Railroad, engine 580, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2604)
      - Northern Pacific Railroad, "Minnetonka", undated (Box 25:, Folder 2605)
      - Northern Pacific Railroad, engine 5000, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2606)
      - Northern Pacific Railroad, engine 5122, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2607)
      - Northern Pacific Central Railroad, "Tomales", undated (Box 25:, Folder 2608)
      - Old Colony & Newport Railroad 4-4-0 on first train from Boston to Orleans, Massachusetts, 1864 (Box 28:, Folder 2874)
      - Old Colony Railroad, "Dorchester", undated (Box 25:, Folder 2609)
      - Old Colony Railroad, "Falmouth", undated (Box 25:, Folder 2610)
      - Old Colony Railroad, "Pawtuxet", undated (Box 25:, Folder 2611)
      - Old Colony Railroad, engine 7, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2612)
      - Old Colony Railroad, engine 67, undated (Box 25:, Folder 2613)
      - Old Colony Railroad, engine 111, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2614)
      - Old Colony Railroad, engine 143, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2615)
      - Old Colony Railroad, engine 199, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2616)
      - Pacific Coast Borax Railroad, "Francis", 1908 (Box 26:, Folder 2617)
      - Pacific Coast Borax Railroad, "Francis", 1908 (Box 26:, Folder 2618)
      - Pacific Coast Borax Railroad, "Francis", 1908 (Box 26:, Folder 2619)
      - Pacific Coast Borax Railroad, "Francis", 1908 (Box 26:, Folder 2620)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 2314, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2621)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 2314, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2622)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 2314, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2623)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 2314, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2624)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 5566, 1971 (Box 26:, Folder 2625)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 5566, 1971 (Box 26:, Folder 2626)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 5595, 1969 (Box 26:, Folder 2627)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 7539, 1970 (Box 26:, Folder 2628)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 7539, 1970 (Box 26:, Folder 2629)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 7539, 1970 (Box 26:, Folder 2630)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 7539, 1970 (Box 26:, Folder 2631)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 8150, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 2632)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 8150, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 2633)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 8150, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 2634)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 8150, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 2635)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 8150, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 2636)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 8472, 1974 (Box 26:, Folder 2637)
      - Penn Central Railroad, engine 8472, 1974 (Box 26:, Folder 2638)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad, engine 2788, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2639)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad, engine 4929, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2640)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad, engine 6100, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2641)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad, engine 6110, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2642)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad, engine 6131, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2643)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad, engine 6200, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2644)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad, engine 8707, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2645)
      - Pennsylvania - Reading Seashore Lines Railroad, engine 6081, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2646)
      - Philippine Railroad, 0-6-2T on passenger train, undated (Box 39:, Folder 4065)
      - Poughkeepsie & Eastern Railroad, engine 1, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2647)
      - Poughkeepsie & Eastern Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2648)
      - Poughkeepsie & Eastern Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2649)
      - Poughkeepsie & Eastern Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2650)
      - Penrhyn Quarry Railroad, "Blanche", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2651)
      - Pere Marquette Railroad, engines 916, 1204 and 1211, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2652)
      - Philadelphia, Reading & New England Railroad, engine 36, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2653)
      - Portable Steam Traction engine, "Excelsior Portable" (not a locomotive), 1882 (Box 27:, Folder 2768)
      - Portland & Ogdensburg Railroad, engine 850, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2654)
      - Portland & Ogdensburg Railroad, engine 950, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2655)
      - Portland & Ogdensburg Railroad, engine 1120, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2656)
      - Portland & Ogdensburg Railroad, engine 1364, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2657)
      - Portland Terminal Railroad, engine 827, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2658)
      - Providence & Worcester Railroad, "Isaac Davis", 1878 (Box 26:, Folder 2659)
      - Providence & Worcester Railroad, "Pawtucket", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2660)
      - Providence, Worcester & Boston Railroad, "Annawamscutt", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2661)
      - P.L.M. Railroad, engine 18, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2662)
      - P.L.M. Railroad, engine 631, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2663)
      - P.L.M. Railroad, engine 2302, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2664)
      - P.L.M. Railroad, engine 2997, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2665)
      - P.L.M. Railroad, unidentified engines, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2666)
      - Rahway Valley Railroad, engine 13, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2667)
      - Rahway Valley Railroad, engine 15, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2668)
      - Reading Railroad, engine 118, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2669)
      - Reading Railroad, engine 2100, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2670)
      - Reading Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2671)
      - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad, engine 88, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2672)
      - Richmond Washington Railroad, "The Carter Braxton", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2673)
      - Robbins Railroad, engine 9, 1941 (Box 26:, Folder 2674)
      - Rock of Ages Railroad, engine 1, 1962 (Box 26:, Folder 2675)
      - Rock of Ages Railroad, engine 7, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2676)
      - Rockport Granite Company Railroad, engine 41, 1904 (Box 26:, Folder 2677)
      - Rocky Nook Railroad, "Smokey Joe", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2678)
      - Rocky Nook Railroad, "Smokey Joe", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2679)
      - Rocky Nook Railroad, "Smokey Joe", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2680)
      - Sabanilla & Maroto F.C. Railroad, "Santiago de Cuba", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2681)
      - Saint Clair Tunnel Railroad, engines 1305 and 1306, 1914 (Box 26:, Folder 2682)
      - Saint Louis & Southern Railroad, engine 778, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2683)
      - Saint Louis & Southwestern Railroad, engine 816, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2684)
      - Sandy River & Rangeley Lakes Railroad, engine 6, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2685)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 100, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2686)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 492, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2687)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 710, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2688)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 910, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2689)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1242, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2690)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1341, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2691)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1357, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2692)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1362, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2693)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1373, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2694)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1663, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2695)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1961, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2696)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1964, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2697)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1968, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2698)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 1987, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2699)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engines 3460, 3461, 3462, 3463 and 3464, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2700)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 3745, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2701)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 3757, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2702)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 3771, 1938 (Box 26:, Folder 2703)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 3785, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2704)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 5000, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2705)
      - Santa Fe Railroad, engine 5004, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2706)
      - Seaboard Airline Railroad, engine 2501, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2707)
      - S.E. & C. Railroad, engine 790, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2708)
      - Shepaug Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2709)
      - S.L.D.W. Company Railroad, "Onward", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2710)
      - Société Nationale des Chemins de fer Français (French National Railway Corporation), U.S. built 141R Class 2-8-2, (builder's plate at Lima, Ohio), undated (Box 28:, Folder 2860)
      - Somerset Railroad, "Carratunk", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2711)
      - Somerset Railroad, "Carratunk", undated (Box 26:, Folder 2712)
      - Somerset & Dorset Junction Railroad, engine 80, undated (Box 26:, Folder 2713)
      - Southern Railroad, engine 6401, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2714)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, engine 894, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2715)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, engine 1100, undated (cyanotype) (Box 27:, Folder 2716)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, engine 1356, undated (cyanotype) (Box 27:, Folder 2717)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, engine 3800, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2718)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, engine 4153, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2719)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, engine 4294, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2720)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, engine 6003, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2721)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, engine 9700, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2722)
      - Southern Pacific Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (cyanotype) (Box 27:, Folder 2723)
      - Springfield Term Railroad, engine 1, 1960 (Box 27:, Folder 2724)
      - Springfield Term Railroad, engine 1, 1960 (Box 27:, Folder 2725)
      - Springfield Term Railroad, engine 1, 1960 (Box 27:, Folder 2726)
      - Springfield Term Railroad, engine 1, 1960 (Box 27:, Folder 2727)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127 (ex-CPR), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2809)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2810)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2811)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2812)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2813)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2814)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2815)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2816)
      - Steamtown Railroad, engine 127, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2817)
      - Steam Village Railroad, unidentified engine, 1971 (Box 27:, Folder 2728)
      - Suncook Valley Railroad, engine 1, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2729)
      - Taunton Branch Railroad, "W.B. Sproat", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2730)
      - Tennessee & West North Carolina Railroad, engine 8, 1935 (Box 27:, Folder 2731)
      - Texas Railroad, "Sable", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2732)
      - Texas Railroad, "The Texas", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2733)
      - Texas & Pacific Railroad, engine 490, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2734)
      - Texas & Pacific Railroad, engine 643, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2735)
      - Texas & Pacific Railroad, engine 909, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2736)
      - Thameshaven Railroad, engine 17, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2737)
      - Union Pacific Railroad, engine 841, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2738)
      - Union Pacific Railroad, engine 3949, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2739)
      - Union Pacific Railroad, engine 4000, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2740)
      - Union Pacific Railroad, engine 4002, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2741)
      - U.S. Army, engine 354, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2742)
      - Virginian Railroad, engine 900, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2743)
      - Wabash Railroad, engine 700, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2744)
      - Warwick Railroad, unidentified engine (steeple cab electric), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2745)
      - Warwick Railroad, unidentified engine (steeple cab electric), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2746)
      - Warwick Railroad, unidentified engine (steeple cab electric), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2747)
      - Western Maryland Railroad, engine 1205, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2748)
      - Western Maryland Railroad, engine 1403, 1947 (Box 27:, Folder 2749)
      - Western Maryland Railroad, engine 3018, 1935 (Box 27:, Folder 2750)
      - Western Maryland Railroad, engine 3018, 1935 (Box 27:, Folder 2751)
      - Western Maryland Railroad, engine 3018, 1935 (Box 27:, Folder 2752)
      - Western Maryland Railroad, engine 3018, 1935 (Box 27:, Folder 2753)
      - Western Railroad (of Massachusetts), "Addison Gilmore", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2758)
      - Wheeling & Lake Erie Railroad, engine 6405, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2754)
      - Wiscasset, Waterville & Farmington Railroad, engine 2, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2755)
      - Wolfeboro Railroad, engine 250, 1977 (Box 27:, Folder 2756)
      - Wolfeboro Railroad, engine 250, 1977 (Box 27:, Folder 2757)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Armorel" (engine 3273), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2759)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Barrington", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2760)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Brunel" (engine 16), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2761)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Charles Saunders" (engine 14), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2762)
      - Unidentified railroad, "City Chester" (engine 3436), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2763)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Cotswold" (engine 3313), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2765)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Durban" (engine 3700), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2766)
      - Unidentified railroad, "East Ardsley" (engine 2), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2767)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Grosvenor" (eingine 3298), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2769)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Hecate" (engine 716), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2770)
      - Unidentified railroad, "King John" (engine 4023), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2771)
      - Unidentified railroad, "La France" (engine 102), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2772)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Lady Disdain" (engine 2907), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2773)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Lebanon", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2774)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Mendip", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2775)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Nelson" (engine 3049), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2776)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Rapid", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2777)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Red Jacket", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2778)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Rhode Island", undated (Box 27:, Folder 2779)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Rising Star" (5007), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2780)